All right, pleased to be joined by my
counterpart in Jacksonville, Bucky
Brooks. Does the sidelines and does a
tremendous job on the sidelines for
Jacksonville Jaguars, NFL media. Bucky,
you're kind of like the wide receiver,
running back slot. You can do it all.
You can return kicks. You do it all in
the media world, man. How you doing?
>> I'm great, man. How how's how's
everything?
>> It How is it to be able to do all those
different things? Being able to cover
the Jags the way you do, then to do all
the stuff you do for the draft, for NFL
media. What's that like kind of being
that weapon X for everybody?
>> Um, look, it's it's it's a lot of fun
because it allows me to kind of stretch
my brain a little bit. Being with the
team is great because I think you
understand the affinity of being with a
team. I think we all love having one
team to kind of root for whatever. But
then the draft is exciting just because
>> it's such a big industry, seeing so many
people here, the fascination about who
is going to be next. And I think the way
the league has done it where turnarounds
can happen quickly in this league,
everyone has optimism. So, you're
looking for the next generation of stars
that can help your team get there.
>> Okay. So, I want to start with that.
Jaguars, the turnaround pretty amazing.
But I want to go to one player in
particular, and I know you know the
player I'm going to ask you about. What
did you see from Trevor Lawrence in 2025
that was different from other years
where that second half of the year where
the Jags go to Denver and put it on a
good Broncos defense? What What hit home
for Trevor this year, Bucky? head coach
confidence relationship [snorts]
and I think so much of what we talk
about often centers around scheme but I
think it's the connectivity it's the
connectivity between the play caller and
the playmaker which is the quarterback
and Liam's confidence in Trevor to say
hey man let it rip don't worry about
mistakes don't worry about turnovers
like just go for it and I'mma back you
think there's something when that
quarterback knows I don't have to look
over my shoulder I don't have to worry
about coming to the sideline getting
chewed out like I can just go play for
Trevor. Um, someone who is, I would say,
a bit of a pleaser in terms he wants to
please everyone around him. I think
having the freedom to just play and not
worry about it, I think it opened up
another part of his game.
>> Talking to JP this week and we centered
on that the second game we played, the
game that Jacksonville played Houston in
Houston. We're down 29-10. We come back,
Davis has this great second half, leads
us to a win. It was the turnaround for
us. It was interesting hearing it from
his perspective how that was also the
turnaround game for Jacksonville. Mark
and I talked about after the game and
said they're done. They had this close
game against the Raiders. We just came
back from behind. They're cooked.
They're done. We know what the Jaguars
are. And the very next week they go and
hammer the Chargers. And that's when we
realized that's a different team. Bucky,
what did you see, especially in that
game against the Chargers that gave you
hope like, hey, this is a different
squad. I'll say before we even get to
the Chargers game, I would say the way
that Liam Cohen handled the locker room
at the end of the Houston game.
>> Very disappointed, very despondent
locker room. And he just thought about,
hey, we got to own it. Yeah. Like this
is a thing where great teams have to
learn how to finish and we have to learn
how to finish. So we got to look inside
and figure out how can we get better at
closing out these games. And so rather
than run from the adversity, he walked
right into it. And that allowed the team
to kind of do some self-reflection and
then come back the next week against a
Chargers team that was really good
>> to knock them off. And then the
confidence started rolling. And you
know, man, everyone is looking for an
edge in this league. And so this team
kind of fed off a little bit of the
underdog mentality, but then more
importantly, they started playing
really, really good football, executing
at every level.
>> You play DB, you know the position, you
know it well, you study it. Travis
Hunter as a DB, what do you expect from
him going forward? Oh, I think it's I
think it's his best position. Uh,
looking into it, if you watch him at
practice, he has some of the best
instincts and ball skills of anyone that
I've been around. And I would say that
at a wide receiver, he catches the ball
naturally. But on defense, man, he is a
C ball getball player. And in a
zonebased scheme where you're allowed to
watch the quarterback and understand how
to make breaks on throws and those
things, it's going to play to his skill
set. And then still being able to come
in on occasion and play wide receiver,
but to me, it's the best move for him
and it's the best move for the team to
put him on As we start thinking about
this draft, Bucky, where's the strength
in this draft? Quarterback people are
talking about, you know, look, it's
Fernando and there's not much else. Hey,
wide receivers got a lot of depth. Maybe
you like the wide receiver position.
Where do you think the where is this
draft in your in your opinion?
>> Yeah, look, wide receivers are solid. I
mean, they're going to be solid wide
receivers taking second through fourth
round, but I feel like it's been like
that for the last five or six years. You
can find guys uh edge rushers are solid.
uh may not be the double- digit guys
that people look after at the top, but
they're gonna be some solid guys that
make contributions. And let's just say
it to be honest, the league is becoming
one where it's by committee when it
comes to accumulating the pass rush. Uh
I would say tight end,
>> nice ice tight end class, guys that can
come in and make things happen. And then
in the secondary, I like the safety
class. I think there's some intrigue and
safety
draft because we don't have the
quarterbacks, but it's one that I think
old school football heads will love
what's coming in. How about the
trenches? What do you think about the
offensive line across the board? Because
it doesn't feel like there's a there's a
Trent Williams. Doesn't feel like
there's Lar Tonsel, but it does feel
like there's some good quality players
at tackle. Then what do you think about
the interior?
>> Yeah, I would say the the tackle class
is interesting because the first time in
a long time people will talk about right
tackles being the marquee position. You
talking about the top two guys at the
top, they are right tackles primarily.
Maui Goa and Spencer Feno, they are
right tackles. And then at left tackle,
you have great athletes, but you may
have some holes in them. Monroe Freeling
from Georgia is a guy who's one-year
player and he moves around well. Blake
Miller from Clemson, super athlete and
those things. Caleb Lemieux from Utah.
So, it's it's interesting on the
interior and on the outside in terms of
doing it. And then on the interior, it's
about trying to find the right fits like
what style of offense do you play? How
do you plug it? So, a lot of it is going
to be the identification of guys that
are perfect fits within your system. I
think I think it's interesting for
interesting for interior defensive
linement kind of the same way kind of
what do you what what's your front
structure? How do you like to use it?
Because I think there's some guys in
this draft I really really like and I
sitting there go for the Texans I don't
know and I know we need bodies. We need
guys that could play alongside Tommy
Togei but as you look at the Jags and we
know we have to go through free agency
bucking but where do you see the needs
kind of for the Jags going forward? Um,
look, I I think for the Jags, look, it's
some guys are available. Like you have
running back that may not be there,
Travis Aten. You have a linebacker,
Devin Lloyd, Y, who may not be
available. So, like those are going to
go to the front of the line. I think on
the defensive line, you need to have a
pass rushing three tech. You have to
have an interior player. Like, when I
look at how do you build your team to
win a division, when I look at the
Texans, the Texans can beat you up on
defense because they have guys all along
the front line that can get to the
quarterback. The Jags need someone that
can do that. So you have Trayvon Walker,
you have Josh Hans Allen who on the
interior can get home. So a young
>> pass rusher on the inside would help.
And then I think you have to continue to
look at safeties and can you find a
playmaking safety that can do it?
Antonio Johnson was terrific. Can you
find someone that can eventually partner
with him all those things in play
without a first round pick is really
about pinpointing who can you find on
day two.
>> You see Antonio Johnson, my body just
cringes. him that with that interception
in week three off the tip pass. I'm just
like, "Oh, Antonio Johnson, I was a big
fan of his coming out of&m."
>> Um,
>> are there any players and look, Sleeper
can be used as, you know, a guy that
should go in the first round, maybe
he'll go in the second or or vice versa.
Do you have any kind of guys that you're
looking at going, you know what, I don't
know that guys are that, you know,
people that are in our business are
talking about this guy or these guys all
that much?
>> Yeah. Should be.
>> Yeah. So, it's interesting because
you're talking about interior offensive
lineman. I'll tell you Chase Bizonitis.
>> Oh, Bantis from
>> Bantis. Bantis from Texas&M. He's He's
good. And his partner on the other side.
Yeah.
>> Reed Adams. Both of those guys can play.
I mean, I I think Rutled the guard from
Georgia Tech is another one. But I would
say like a guy
>> Thenman,
>> the safety from Oregon who played at
Purdue. It is rare that you have someone
who can lead um with six interceptions
as a freshman and then the next year
come and lead his team in tackles,
right? and then go to Oregon and play in
the box and play nickel safety. He has a
lot of traits and they say that he's
going to blow it up when it comes to a
physical specimen. He's going to be
someone to watch.
>> I hope to God he does not get to 52 in
the Jaguars. I'll lose.
>> Oh, he won't be there. Like, we talking
about a first round guy. I certainly
>> Exactly. I think this week solidifies
him. I think he's kind of lying in the
weeds and he tests. It's going to be
like, "Hey, what about this safety from
Morgan?" I'm like, "Hey, we've been
talking about this guy for a while."
Bucky, you do a hell of a job with the
Jaguars. You do a hell of a job with NFL
media, man. Really appreciate your time.
Thank you, brother.